<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <docs>https://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <title>Blog Management on Disciple School</title>
    <link>https://discipleschool.com/categories/blog-management/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog Management on Disciple School</description>
    <image>
      <title>Blog Management on Disciple School</title>
      <link>https://discipleschool.com/categories/blog-management/</link>
      <url>images/jason-red-tritone-16x9.jpg</url>
    </image>
    <ttl>1440</ttl>
    <generator>Hugo 0.54.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 17:41:35 UT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://discipleschool.com/categories/blog-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Learning in Public</title>
      <link>https://discipleschool.com/post/learning-in-public/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Jason West</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://discipleschool.com/post/learning-in-public/</guid>
      <description>The Wrong Approach I&amp;rsquo;ve spent the last several years trying to learn as much as possible and put it all together into one big project that I could share with the people. But as I&amp;rsquo;m reading one book, I find that it leads to a dozen more, and I start reading those books - and all the books they reference while I&amp;rsquo;m still reading through the original book that piqued my interest.</description>
      <category domain="https://discipleschool.com/categories/blog-management">Blog Management</category>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[ The Wrong Approach I&amp;rsquo;ve spent the last several years trying to learn as much as possible and put it all together into one big project that I could share with the people. But as I&amp;rsquo;m reading one book, I find that it leads to a dozen more, and I start reading those books - and all the books they reference while I&amp;rsquo;m still reading through the original book that piqued my interest. Obviously, I&amp;rsquo;ll never be able to finish them all. I will never be able to review all of the information, which means that - unless I change my approach - I will never be able to even begin sharing anything.
The problem is that I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking of this website as a place where I can publish some completed bible lessons that might help others become disciples of Jesus, and make more disciples. But as I mentioned, I&amp;rsquo;m constantly finding new information that I might want to add.
What if I started using this website as a publicly-accessible filing cabinet of thoughts and ideas that have stuck with me from the books and articles I&amp;rsquo;ve recently read? That might cause me to stop thinking of each post as something that needs to be well-structured, and to start thinking of each post as simply a new scrap of paper or index card with another idea or quote that I want to keep. Something to be jotted down that I could come back to later in order to connect it with other ideas to in order to form my own ideas.
I tend to think of each post as if it were going to be permenant, and therefore needed to be carefully constructed because it cannot be undone or altered once it&amp;rsquo;s shared. Where did this idea come from? I don&amp;rsquo;t know. But it isn&amp;rsquo;t helpful to me at all.
A New Approach Instead, I need to be willing to - as one person put it - &amp;ldquo;learn in public.&amp;rdquo; To set all of my resources on the table and start talking my way through the data in a way that anyone can observe. I could share things as often as possible and let others know what I&amp;rsquo;m working on, what questions I have, etc&amp;hellip; There may be others out there who are wresting with the same problems and questions. We could share the work. Create a sort of collective genius, or &amp;ldquo;scenius&amp;rdquo; - a concept attributed to musician Brian Eno. I first read about the concept of &amp;ldquo;scenius&amp;rdquo; in a book called Show Your Work by Austin Kleon. Here&amp;rsquo;s what Eno says about it:
  So I thought that originally those few individuals who’d survived in history – in the sort-of “Great Man” theory of history – they were called “geniuses”. But what I thought was interesting was the fact that they all came out of a scene that was very fertile and very intelligent. So I came up with this word “scenius” – and scenius is the intelligence of a whole… operation or group of people. And I think that’s a more useful way to think about culture, actually. I think that – let’s forget the idea of “genius” for a little while, let’s think about the whole ecology of ideas that give rise to good new thoughts and good new work. Brian Eno  In his book 5Q (about the five-fold ministry), Alan Hirsch mentions Eno&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;scenius&amp;rdquo; concept as a new way of thinking about how the church should be operating.
When we share ideas and allow others access to our work, we increase the likelihood that others can copy ideas from us (that we received from others they may not know about), and share ideas with us (that they recieved from others we may not know about). All of those ideas can interact with one another and form connections to ther ideas until those connections reveal a bigger picture than could have been imagined by any single one of us if we all had worked alone.
I need to be willing to bring people into the process that goes on behind the scenes. Show people how I get ideas. Become a documentarian of what I do. Interestingly, as I&amp;rsquo;m reading back over this post, it occurs to me that this is exactly what disciple makers do. They allow other people into their lives in a very informal and personal way.
This may be very difficult for me at first. I&amp;rsquo;ll try to do a &amp;ldquo;daily dispatch,&amp;rdquo; but it may be more of a weekly thing for awhile.
Seth Godin recommends daily blogging as well.
He suggests that even if nobody reads the posts, the act of writing them every day is beneficial to the author because it helps to clarify one&amp;rsquo;s thoughts. He&amp;rsquo;s not alone in that. As Dawson Trotman (founder of The Navigators) said:   &amp;#34;Thoughts disentangle themselves as they pass through lips and fingertips.&amp;#34; Dawson Trotman  When we&amp;rsquo;re forced with trying to communicate our ideas, our brain begins the work of trying to arrange our thoughts into something sensible and communicable.
So, that&amp;rsquo;s the next phase. This website is my own public filing cabinet where I freely share ideas and document how and where I came up with them.
The idea is to allow the audience to follow along as I try to figure out how to make disciples of Jesus.
Do you have a process for gathering information? For organizing it? What apps do you use? Do you do any analog note-taking?
Photo by Sanwal Deen on Unsplash.
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock and Flow</title>
      <link>https://discipleschool.com/post/stock-and-flow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 00:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Jason West</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://discipleschool.com/post/stock-and-flow/</guid>
      <description>Austin Kleon wrote a great book about creativity and audience-building that I&amp;rsquo;ve read multiple times. It&amp;rsquo;s called Show Your Work, and I highly recommend it for anyone who&amp;rsquo;s ever wondered aloud, &amp;ldquo;How do I get my stuff out there? How do I get noticed? How do I find an audience?&amp;rdquo;
There&amp;rsquo;s a great section in the book called &amp;ldquo;Stock and Flow,&amp;rdquo; where Kleon mentions an article that economist Robin Sloan wrote in 2010.</description>
      <category domain="https://discipleschool.com/categories/blog-management">Blog Management</category>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Austin Kleon wrote a great book about creativity and audience-building that I&amp;rsquo;ve read multiple times. It&amp;rsquo;s called Show Your Work, and I highly recommend it for anyone who&amp;rsquo;s ever wondered aloud, &amp;ldquo;How do I get my stuff out there? How do I get noticed? How do I find an audience?&amp;rdquo;
There&amp;rsquo;s a great section in the book called &amp;ldquo;Stock and Flow,&amp;rdquo; where Kleon mentions an article that economist Robin Sloan wrote in 2010. In the article, she mentions the economic concepts of stock and flow. She defines stock as anything having static value - like a specific amount of money in the bank, or a certain number trees in the forest. Flow is a rate of change. For example, fifteen dollars per hour or three thousand toothpicks per day.
She then uses those concepts as a metaphor for modern media consumption. I think it&amp;rsquo;s a useful metaphor for anyone interested in developing content or becoming an influencer.
She says:  Flow is the feed. It’s the posts and the tweets. It’s the stream of daily and sub-daily updates that reminds people you exist. Stock is the durable stuff. It’s the content you produce that’s as interesting in two months (or two years) as it is today. It’s what people discover via search. It’s what spreads slowly but surely, building fans over time. Robin Sloan  She goes on to say that the magic formula is to maintain a flow (tweets and posts) while working on your stock (evergreen content) in the background.
The Stock and Flow analogy reminded me of something I read about Malcolm Gladwell&amp;rsquo;s process for becoming a best-selling author of category-busting books like The Tipping Point. He obviously gained valuable experience writing articles for the New Yorker magazine, but perhaps more importantly, he was able to explore and develop ideas and content that he would later use in his best-selling books.
If we think of those books as his stock, then those articles in the New Yorker would be his flow. (Any of us might feel that having an article published in the New Yorker would be our stock, but this is Malcolm Gladwell we&amp;rsquo;re talking about here.)
Shawn Coyne is an editor at Black Irish Books and the author of The Story Grid. He created a podcast series analyzing the process behind the development of The Tipping Point. In the episode entitled, &amp;ldquo;Out of the Rabbit Hole,&amp;rdquo; he talks about stock and flow, but he uses the Hebrew concepts of &amp;ldquo;kavanah&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;matarah.&amp;rdquo;
Here&amp;rsquo;s that segment in its entirety:  Just before the Israeli military’s blitzkrieg offensive against the allied Arab nations massed at its borders in 1967, the word repeated over and over again on Air Force bases and on the sands of the Sinai was “Kavanah.” Kavanah means grand intention. The Sabras were instructed to remember just one thing when the chaos of combat overwhelmed them: &amp;#34;Remember the Kavanah.&amp;#34; For the pilots their global mission was to wipe out Arab airstrips while defending Israeli airspace. If they took care of the airstrips, defending the air space would be a hell of a lot easier…. For the ground troops, it was to keep moving forward…to reach and seize the Suez Canal. Taking the Suez Canal would inevitably lead to international intervention… The United States and the U.S.S.R. would jump into the fray if the canal were at stake. Together, those two missions would add up to Israel’s security…at least until the next mobilization of Arab forces. Kavanahs are not Matarahs, which are building block objectives. (For us writers Matarahs are daily word counts or scene objectives or outlines). Kavanahs are the global intention. So when pilots lost course on their way to destroy Arab air bases, they did not panic. They realized that while they would not accomplish the immediate Matarah objective, bombing the specific base they’d been assigned, they could still chip away at the Kavanah by bombing another airstrip in their path. Shawn Coyne  What Shawn Coyne calls the &amp;ldquo;Kavanah,&amp;rdquo; or global intention, Robin Sloan calls &amp;ldquo;stock.&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s the end game that we hope to accomplish. It&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;the entity.&amp;rdquo;
Matarot (plural form of matarah), are the daily objectives, the short-term goals that (ideally) move us towards the kavanah.
My kavanah / stock / grand intention is to write a book or make something that helps people become and produce disciples of Jesus Christ. The rough draft of that book can be found here. Updates to that site will be less frequent.
In the meantime, I will use this site as a platform for distributing my matarot, building block content. I will repeat myself often, experimenting with different ways of attacking a problem, probing for the most effective arguments, analogies and language that will ultimately be used in the book - my grand intention.
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
