<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Disciple School</title>
    <link>https://discipleschool.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Disciple School</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://discipleschool.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Becoming and Producing Disciples of Jesus Christ</title>
      <link>https://discipleschool.com/post/becoming-and-producing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://discipleschool.com/post/becoming-and-producing/</guid>
      <description>The Discipleship Crisis The Great Commission has been worshipped, but not obeyed. The church has tried to get world evangelization without disciple making.
Bill Hull, The Disciple-Making Pastor (Grand Rapids, Mich.: Revell, 1988)  I&amp;rsquo;m compelled to tell you something that may be difficult for you to hear.
Your church has a serious problem.
I&amp;rsquo;m sure that you&amp;rsquo;d love to respond by telling me the size of your congregation, the amount of giving, your service to the poor, or the number of new converts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The &#39;End&#39; Game: End-times and the End of Our Credibility</title>
      <link>https://discipleschool.com/post/the-end-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://discipleschool.com/post/the-end-game/</guid>
      <description>Feathers for Worms I&amp;rsquo;m concerned that focusing our attention on &amp;ldquo;end-of-the-world&amp;rdquo; prophecies could bring an end to our credibility. Sharing social media posts about the latest apocalyptic theories from doomsday preachers could cost you more than you realize.
Let&amp;rsquo;s begin with a parable. One day long ago, over the hot sands of a Middle Eastern country, a white skylark flew in joyous loops about the sky. As she swooped near the earth, she heard a merchant cry out, &amp;ldquo;Worms!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stock and Flow</title>
      <link>https://discipleschool.com/post/stock-and-flow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://discipleschool.com/post/stock-and-flow/</guid>
      <description>Austin Kleon wrote a great book about creativity and audience-building that I&amp;rsquo;ve read multiple times. It&amp;rsquo;s called Show Your Work, and I highly recommend it for anyone who&amp;rsquo;s ever wondered aloud, &amp;ldquo;How do I get my stuff out there? How do I get noticed? How do I find an audience?&amp;rdquo;
There&amp;rsquo;s a great section in the book called &amp;ldquo;Stock and Flow,&amp;rdquo; where Kleon mentions an article that economist Robin Sloan wrote in 2010.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recommended Content</title>
      <link>https://discipleschool.com/page/bibliography/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://discipleschool.com/page/bibliography/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a collection of Books, Websites, Podcasts and Videos I wanted to make you aware of.
As I continue to add more items to these lists, I may take the time to categorize them by topic.
Books -
Websites -
Podcasts -
Videos Everything&amp;rsquo;s a Remix</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanks for Subscribing</title>
      <link>https://discipleschool.com/page/success/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://discipleschool.com/page/success/</guid>
      <description>Thanks for subscribing!
Catch up on some of our most recent posts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>