<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <docs>https://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <title>Pages on Disciple School</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Disciple School</description>
    <image>
      <title>Pages on Disciple School</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/page/</link>
      <url>images/jason-red-tritone-16x9.jpg</url>
    </image>
    <ttl>1440</ttl>
    <generator>Hugo 0.62.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 03:31:05 UT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lesson Plan</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/page/lesson-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Jason West</dc:creator>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/page/lesson-plan/</guid>
      <description>The first draft is you, telling yourself the story.
Terry Pratchett  I&#39;m not writing a book, but I like the concept of starting a project by telling myself the story. I will follow Pratchett&#39;s advice and simply walk myself through the argument that I&#39;ll present on Disciple School.
I have a difficult time recognizing when a given piece of content is ready to be published. For some reason, I have a difficult time publishing small chunks of information about any given subject.</description>
      <category domain="http://localhost:1313/categories/"></category>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[  The first draft is you, telling yourself the story.
Terry Pratchett  I&#39;m not writing a book, but I like the concept of starting a project by telling myself the story. I will follow Pratchett&#39;s advice and simply walk myself through the argument that I&#39;ll present on Disciple School.
I have a difficult time recognizing when a given piece of content is ready to be published. For some reason, I have a difficult time publishing small chunks of information about any given subject. I tend to want an exhaustive summary of that subject before presenting it publicly. As a result, I spend a great deal of time collecting information, and not nearly enough time creating content.
I&#39;m trying to get myself past that by forcing myself into a publishing schedule, which will require me to publish things way before I think they&#39;re ready.
I&#39;ll start posting articles on here in small chunks, and allow the final version to develop over time. I wrote a post about the concept called learning in public, I just never implemented it.
I don&#39;t really have an editorial calendar in place, but I do have a roadmap of subjects that I will be addressing. Rather than completing them in some linear order, I&#39;ll start adding to them piece by piece and allow them to develop over time.
Here&#39;s a list of posts that I&#39;m currently working on:
 It&#39;s my opinion that Christianity is failing. But it&#39;s not just an opinion. I can prove it.
Define &amp;lsquo;failure.&amp;rsquo;
Variables contributing to our failure.
 ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recommended Content</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/page/bibliography/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 00:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Jason West</dc:creator>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/page/bibliography/</guid>
      <description>Here&#39;s a collection of Books, Websites, Podcasts and Videos I wanted to make you aware of.
As I continue to add more items to these lists, I may take the time to categorize them by topic.
Books    Websites    Podcasts    Videos Everything&#39;s a Remix</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Here&#39;s a collection of Books, Websites, Podcasts and Videos I wanted to make you aware of.
As I continue to add more items to these lists, I may take the time to categorize them by topic.
Books    Websites    Podcasts    Videos Everything&#39;s a Remix
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thanks for Subscribing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/page/success/</link>
      <dc:creator>Jason West</dc:creator>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/page/success/</guid>
      <description>Catch up on some of our most recent posts.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Catch up on some of our most recent posts.
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
