<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <docs>https://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <title>mobile on Disciple School</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/mobile/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mobile on Disciple School</description>
    <image>
      <title>mobile on Disciple School</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/mobile/</link>
      <url>images/jason-red-tritone-16x9.jpg</url>
    </image>
    <ttl>1440</ttl>
    <generator>Hugo 0.62.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 03:19:50 UT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/mobile/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Half the World is Now Online</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/half-the-world-is-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Jason West</dc:creator>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/half-the-world-is-online/</guid>
      <description>There are almost 4 billion people using the internet! What would the Apostle Paul have done if he could&#39;ve communicated with 4 billion people with such little difficulty? What could you and I be doing to reach the masses?</description>
      <category domain="http://localhost:1313/categories/evangelism">Evangelism</category>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[This is what I added on 12-32-2019. I just read that More than half of global population now online: UN
Highlights from the article:
  According to the UN, 3.9 billion people are now using the Internet, meaning that for the first time more than half of the global population is online.
  Land-lines are disappearing, but the number of mobile-cellular telephone subscriptions is now greater than the global population.
  Mobile broadband subscriptions have skyrocketed from just four subscriptions per 100 inhabitants in 2007 to 69.3 today.
  There are currently a full 5.3 billion active mobile broadband subscriptions worldwide.
  Nearly the entire world population, a full 96 percent, now lives within reach of a mobile cellular network, and 90 percent of people can access the Internet through a 3G or higher speed network.
  Whenever I hear stats like these, I can&#39;t help but think about the amazing opportunities to share the gospel. There are almost 4 billion people using the internet! What would the Apostle Paul have done if he could&#39;ve communicated with 4 billion people with such little difficulty? What could you and I be doing to reach the masses?
  Start a blog. There are lots of free options:
 Wordpress Wix Medium Weebly    Or you could simply post some content on your social media account. Facebook still has a huge audience. Or you could s try to start an account on social networking sites that are popular in other countries, and try to connect with people.
  Start accounts on video sharing sites and make some content. YouTube is still king when it comes to video. But other options include Vimeo and Twitch.
  ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
