<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <docs>https://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <title>Church Model on Disciple School</title>
    <link>https://discipleschool.com/categories/church-model/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Church Model on Disciple School</description>
    <image>
      <title>Church Model on Disciple School</title>
      <link>https://discipleschool.com/categories/church-model/</link>
      <url>images/jason-red-tritone-16x9.jpg</url>
    </image>
    <ttl>1440</ttl>
    <generator>Hugo 0.54.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 17:41:35 UT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://discipleschool.com/categories/church-model/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Most Dangerous Doctrine</title>
      <link>https://discipleschool.com/post/the-most-dangerous-doctrine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 00:00:00 UT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>Jason West</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://discipleschool.com/post/the-most-dangerous-doctrine/</guid>
      <description>Bible warns us against allowing false doctrines into the church&amp;hellip;
Never Question the Pastor. Of all the destructive false doctrines that could destroy a church, the most dangerous is that we should never question the leaders.
Think of it, if we can challenge, test and question the decisions and actions of our leaders, it would be most difficult for them to implement anything that could potentially harm the church or any of its members.</description>
      <category domain="https://discipleschool.com/categories/church-model">Church Model</category>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[ Bible warns us against allowing false doctrines into the church&amp;hellip;
Never Question the Pastor. Of all the destructive false doctrines that could destroy a church, the most dangerous is that we should never question the leaders.
Think of it, if we can challenge, test and question the decisions and actions of our leaders, it would be most difficult for them to implement anything that could potentially harm the church or any of its members. After all, anyone with a concern could simply present it to those with influence and authority. If the pastor&amp;rsquo;s thinking or behavior was found to be self-serving, or contrary to Scripture, the elders would confront the pastor and present their case to the pastor.
However, if nobody is allowed to question the words and actions of the pastor, how can any wrong thinking or behavior ever be challenged?
For example, if a pastor was involved in some business arrangement that was unethical - and maybe even illegal - how could anyone ever confront his behavior?
Go to the Pastor? If they went to the pastor about it, he could simply say, &amp;ldquo;I am ordering you not to tell anyone else about this. And since I&amp;rsquo;m the pastor, you cannot disobey me.&amp;rdquo; Then what? The matter could ever be addressed again.
Go to the Board? If instead the concerned person went to the board and told them of their findings, the board members could simply say, &amp;ldquo;Well, we cannot question the man of God. Shame on you for saying anything negative against him.&amp;rdquo; Or, they could take the matter to the pastor, who could say to them, &amp;ldquo;I am ordering you not to tell anyone else about this. And since I&amp;rsquo;m the pastor, you cannot disobey me.&amp;rdquo; Then what? The matter could ever be addressed again.
Let God Handle It? You may say, &amp;ldquo;Well, we&amp;rsquo;ll just have to wait for God to handle it. If the pastor is wrong, God will stop him.&amp;rdquo; Are you sure about that? Have you ever heard of Jim Jones? He led nearly one thousand people to commit mass suicide. Why didn&amp;rsquo;t God stop him?
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
